softlow.com 2005-05-11

# Privacy Policy

| 

##### Cracks notice  
  
---  
  
######  You won't find Crack, Serial or Keygen at our site. We disparage using of any type of cracking or hacking software. Using cracks, key generators, illegal serial numbers and registration codes prevents developing new software. Buying Software you are getting high quality safety software and guaranteed program support by Author.   
  
### Privacy Policy

SoftLow.com takes your privacy seriously. Because we gather certain types of information about our users we want to help you understand the terms and conditions surrounding the collection and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. These privacy practices apply to the Website that you were viewing when you clicked through to this policy, which is operated by SoftLow.com, its partner or affiliate. This site contains links to other sites. SoftLow.com.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. 

**Usage Tracking**

SoftLow.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout SoftLow.com.com and this information is correlated with data about individual users. Overall usage statistics, according to a user's domain name, browser type and MIME type gotten by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser), are also broken down. SoftLow.com also tracks and catalogs the search terms that customers enter into our search tools, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. 

**IP & Log files**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. We will not use this information in any other way and will not release the information to any third parties. 

SoftLow.com automatically logs the following information about visitors to this website: IP addresses, browser type, domain names, access times and the number of hits to specific pages within the site. This information is used to administer the site and to evaluate its usability. This information is not used to create any type of personal profiles for the visitors. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Use of software author names, addresses and any other personal information is used only in our announcements and is not released to third parties nor do we send any mail to the return addresses offering or soliciting any services. 

**Contacting the WebSite**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can mail to [support@softlow.com](mailto:support@softlow.com) or contact us via form on this website.
